http://www.acuhealthcare.com/privacy-policy

Privacy policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for S3 Stores, Inc. websites. We take our obligations with regard to your personal information seriously, and have created this privacy policy to inform you of the information gathering and dissemination practices of this website. In wishing to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information-collecting practices and to notify you of:
what personally identifiable information (or third party personally identifiable information) of yours is collected from you through our website the organization collecting the information how the information is used with whom the information may be shared what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information the kind of security procedures that are in place to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of information under S3 Stores, Inc. control how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
If you feel that S3 Stores, Inc. is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, please contact us. Information Collection and Use S3 Stores, Inc. is the sole owner of the information we collect on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this policy statement. S3 Stores, Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on this website. Membership When you make a purchase on our website, you choose to become a member. You provide the following information to S3 Stores, Inc.:
Your name Your email address Your billing and shipping address Your telephone number Your form of payment You choose your own member identification and password to use for all future purchases on the site. You choose whether or not you would like to receive electronic mailings from S3 Stores, Inc.
Ordering We request information from the user on our order form when making a purchase. Here, a user must provide his/her contact and other information, (name and shipping address, shipping information, and form of payment). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill the customer's order. If we have difficulty processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the customer. Sharing S3 Stores, Inc. does not share your private information with other companies. However, we may use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. These companies may collect additional information if needed to provide you with the requested services. Cookies S3 Stores, Inc. sites employ web browser cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. S3 Stores, Inc. uses cookies to identify your visit session for customizing your user experience, for creating web site analytical data, and for Google Display Advertising and Remarketing with Google AdWords on third party websites. We use both session and persistent cookies. The website visitor may use features of their web browser to block or delete S3 Stores, Inc. cookies, cookies used for Google AdWords, and/or cookies used for Google Display Advertising and Remarketing with Google Adwords from the user's hard drive or memory. However, by disabling cookies, certain site features and functionality may no longer work properly, and the user may not see advertising on third party websites with reminders and special offers. You can opt out of Google Display Advertising and Remarketing with Google Adwords by visiting their website and following the instructions presented on the page. Usage Tracking S3 Stores, Inc. database tracks the traffic throughout our site. This information is used to compile overall statistics and is not recorded at an individual level. This includes IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and # of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, and track user movement in the aggregate. The statistics help us decide which products and services best serve our guests. Aggregate Information S3 Stores, Inc. uses aggregate information from demographic surveys, traffic patterns and IP addresses to customize our site. Aggregate information is occasionally shared with partners of S3 Stores, Inc. to plan advertising or promotions. We do not share any personally identifiable information. Surveys S3 Stores, Inc. may conduct surveys and other studies of its user base and make use of the results for marketing and planning purposes. Participation in such surveys is at the user's option. We reserve the right to disclose information provided by any user through a survey, provided that no personal information identifying that user is disclosed. Circumstances under which S3 Stores, Inc. would publicly disclose aggregate information include, but are not limited to, sharing survey results with partners and/or site users, business planning, and publicizing overall usage data in press communications. Newsletters, Catalogs, Etc. From time to time users may be given the opportunity to "opt-in" to receive site notifications, newsletters, or other information via email. Users may remove themselves from such services at their discretion. Any email sent to an "opt-in" list will include directions for how a user may remove himself or herself from the list, or a URL where the user may find such directions. If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, catalog, etc., we ask for contact information such as name, street address and email address to provide these communications. Out of respect for our users' privacy we provide ways to opt-out of these communications. On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send you an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though you can deactivate your account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. Tell-A-Friend If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about us or an item on our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. S3 Stores, Inc. will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. We do store the friend's email and they have an option to opt-out in the communication. Special Request Pages Our customers can use our special request pages to inquire about products that they cannot find on the website, for special orders for example. Personal information is gathered during this process, and is used strictly for the purposes of replying to user inquiries, billing purposes and to fill customers' orders. Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your phone, email or address), or if a user no longer desires our services, we offer ways to correct, update or delete/deactivate that user's personally identifiable information provided to us. Links This website contains links to other sites, whether owned or controlled by S3 Stores, Inc., or unrelated third parties. Please be aware that the privacy policies of those sites may differ from those of S3 Stores, Inc., and that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by S3 Stores, Inc. Online Security S3 Stores, Inc. takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via our website, we take steps to protect your information both online and offline. To secure site integrity, we employ measures, including but not limited to security audits, use of encryption tools and software, and other reasonable security measures and procedures. When a PayPal / 2CheckOut order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the standard encryption software in the industry - Secure Socket Layers (SSLs). While on a secure page, such as our order form, a lock icon appears in your Web browser. When you are not on a secure page, no lock icon will appear. PayPal / 2CheckOut uses SSL encryption to protect sensitive information (like your credit card information) online. Offline Security and Privacy We do everything in our power to protect user information offline. All user information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, all employees are fully informed about our security and privacy practices and are dutifully updated as new policies are added or revised. They are regularly notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure that customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment under restricted access. In the event that S3 Stores, Inc. becomes aware that site security is compromised or nonpublic user information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including but not limited to external security attacks, we shall take reasonable measures which we deem appropriate, including but not limited to internal investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities, notwithstanding other provisions of this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about security on our websites, please contact us. Privacy Policy Changes In the event of any changes to S3 Stores, Inc. Privacy Policy, we will post the changes to this page and other places we deem appropriate, so that our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We use information only in accordance with the privacy policy under which that information was collected. If at any time we plan on using your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated in this policy at the time of collection, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice to allow or disallow us to use your information in this manner. If you have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated your account, you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our website notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. Last modified: 8-19-13
You recently viewed items
Departments
Orthopedic Supplies
CPM Machines
(4)
Traction Equipment
(27)
Foot Braces
(17)
Neck Braces
(1)
Arm Slings
(1)
Head Protectors
(5)
Arm & Elbow Braces
(5)
Diabetic Supplies
Insulin Syringes
(9)
Lancets & Insulin Pen Needles
(213)
Glucose Test Strips & Control Solutions
(8)
Glucose Meters
(2)
Diabetic Skin Care
(1)
Massage Supplies
Massage Tools
(24)
Massage Lotions & Creams
(31)
Disinfectant Sprays
(4)
Gel Warmers
(8)
Massage Bolsters
(9)
Exam Table Paper
(4)
Fitness Supplies
Foam Rollers
(134)
Hand Exercisers
(92)
Exercise Bands
(76)
Stretch Out Straps
(3)
Balance Trainer
(112)
Fitness Equipment
(19)
Fitness Tools
(125)
Exercise Mats
(33)
Pain Cure
Paraffin Baths
(25)
Heat & Cold Therapy
(289)
Electrotherapy Machines & Supplies
(82)
Light Therapy Equipment
(15)
New Products
Bathroom Safety
(2)
Canes
(13)
Commodes
(2)
Electrotherapy
(1)
Personal Care
(3037)
Power Mobility
(1)
Pressure Prevention
(11)
Respiratory
(1256)
Rollators
(1)
Walkers
(8)
Pediatric Rehab
(53)
Massage
(90)
Hot & Cold Therapy
(106)
Exercise
(706)
ADL
(49)
Splints & Support
(744)
Evaluation
(272)
DME
(47)
Modalities
(226)
Treatment Furniture
(19)
Pediatric
(86)
Hydrotherapy
(88)
NICU and Infant Care
(193)
Infection Control
(915)
Diagnostic Tools
(2515)
Laboratory Supplies
(2879)
Diagnostic Tests
(530)
Exam Room Equipment
(6301)
Olark live chat software
(5)
Defibrillators
(256)
Surgical Supplies
(2043)
Orthopedic Therapy
(4727)
Massage Therapy
(216)
Exam Room Furniture
(4150)
Blood Pressure Monitor
(2509)
Medical Organizers
(32)
Stethoscopes
(703)
IV Administration
(738)
Interventional Imaging
(68)
Patient Care
(1818)
EMS Supplies
(2916)
Obstetrics & Gynecology
(130)
Exercise Equipment
(2186)
Wound Care
(1630)
zz
(7)
Mobility
(2389)
Incontinence Care
(730)
Diabetic
(225)
Needles & Syringes
(317)
Instruments
(240)
Dentistry
(86)
Ostomy Supplies
(494)
Disposable Gloves
(216)
Urology
(732)
Pediatrics
(453)
Office Supplies
(248)
Educational Products
(706)
Health Care
(148)
Gloves
(60)
Fab-10-0065-10
(1)
Smd-yc-8
(1)
Bd-581040
(1)
Bd-405180-1
(1)
Alt-59390017518
(1)
Smd-225-3703-810
(1)
Hs-1126148
(1)
Hs-1227108
(1)
Hs-904472
(1)
Qua-230005
(1)
Test-test
(1)
Exp-ak-04020
(1)
Covid-19 related
(34)
Patient positioners
(113)
Ergonomics
(229)
Operating room
(656)
Emergency preparedness
(38)
Podiatry
(77)
Medical imaging
(128)
Rehabilitation & physical therapy
(259)
Diagnostic and evaluation tools
(39)
Adl - aids for daily living
(133)
Durable medical equipment
(174)
Speech and language
(189)
Splints and braces
(204)
Footwear, insoles, inserts
(44)
Medical carts
(54)
Radiation protection
(63)
Fall management
(84)
Clinic & hospital supplies, equipment, furnishings
(45)
Wheelchair cushions
(25)
Bariatrics, obesity
(82)
Never events
(14)
Patient safety straps
(14)
Safe patient handling and transfer
(16)
Medical staff ppe
(5)
Goj-9652-12-1
(1)
Clearance!!
(12)
General nursing and patient care
(14)
Nutritional and feeding
(6)
Equipment and furnishings
(1)
Incontinence
(10)
Ostomy and urology
(1)
Gowns
(9)
Wipes
(17)
Shoe covers
(1)
3 ply
(16)
Thermometers
(8)
Reusable
(121)
Hand sanitizers
(98)
Kn95
(13)
Face shields
(25)
Disinfectants
(6)
N95
(3)
Ppe kits
(9)
Cellphone accessories
(1)
Protective wear
(14)
Sanitizers, disinfectants, & wipes
(15)
Face shields & goggles
(3)
Maternity Supplies
Hip Braces
(2)
Prenatal Cradle
(8)
V2 Supporter
(2)
Hydrotherapy Equipment
Hydrotherapy Whirlpools
(1)
Negative Ion Products
Wristbands
(2)
Belts
(1)
Health Supplements
IV Therapy Supplies
Assistive Furniture
Hospital Beds & Accessories
(424)
Healthcare Recliners
(9)
Overbed Tables
(21)
Medical Stools
(7)
Medical Step Stools
(4)
Bathroom Safety Products
(265)
Wheelchair Ramps
(6)
Utility Carts
(72)
Medical Stands
(4)
Hospital Screens
(5)
Medical Hampers
(24)
Treatment Tables
(6)
Assistive Chairs
(19)
Daily Living Aids
Non-Slip Mats & Supplies
(175)
Dressing Aids
(6)
Reaching Tools & Openers
(6)
Eating & Drinking Aids
(45)
Mobility Aids
Positioning Aids
(26)
Special Seat Belts
(1)
Canes
(65)
Crutches
(30)
Knee Walkers
(1)
Patient Lifts
(14)
Mobility Accessories
(55)
Rollators
(59)
Medical Walkers
(55)
Wheelchairs
(175)
Wheelchairs Accessories
(87)
Gait Trainers
(15)
Lift Slings
(34)
Transfer Boards
(9)
Diagnostic Equipment
Scoliosis Measurement
(7)
Sit & Reach Box
(2)
Spirometer
(5)
Sensor Pads
(25)
Blood Pressure Monitors
(29)
Body Fat Analyzers
(16)
Stethoscopes
(2)
Pulse Oximeters
(3)
Medical Thermometer
(1)
Weight Scales & Height Rods
(4)
Tuning Forks
(26)
Reflex & Neurology Tools
(38)
Finger Probe
(6)
Patient Alarms
(19)
Examination Light
(4)
Ultrasound Gel & Lotion
(25)
Sensation Testing Tools
(53)
Strength Measurement
(6)
Inclinometers & Goniometers
(35)
Dynamometers
(14)
Dolorimeter
(5)
Finger Circumference Gauge
(2)
Medical Measuring Tapes
(15)
Breadth Calipers
(2)
Hand Evaluation Kits
(4)
Incontinence Supplies
Bedpans & Urinals
(3)
Underpads
(1)
Respiratory Supplies
Air Purifiers & Humidifiers
(2)
Respiratory Accessories
(45)
Nebulizers
(5)
Wound Care Supplies
Alcohol Prep Pads
(1)
Band Aids
(2)
Bandages
(54)
Bariatrics, obesity
Bariatric bath safety
(10)
Respiratory
(5)
Bariatric wheelchair essentials
(1)
Bariatric mobility
(7)
Bariatric bed positioning
(3)
Bariatric patient handling
(14)
Bariatric beds and bed safety
(4)
Bariatric patient o.r. accommodations
(6)
Bariatric clinical furniture
(15)
Bariatric specialty seating
(7)
Bariatric scales
(9)
Mri safe bariatric equipment
(3)
Bariatric wheelchair cushions
(13)
Safe patient handling and transfer
Gait belts
(9)
Shifters and transfer boards
(5)
Patient lifts
(1)
Slings
(7)
Patient transfer aids
(4)
Patient safety straps
Armboard straps
(2)
Surgical table straps
(11)
Vericlean patient straps
(2)
Alistrap®
(4)
Strap accessories
(2)
Medical imaging
Mri equipment & supplies
(54)
Imaging tables & chairs
(3)
Nuclear medicine
(5)
Lighting & magnifiers
(23)
X-ray grid protectors
(9)
Cardiac cath accessories
(13)
Ultrasound supplies
(18)
Radiation immobilization
(2)
Mammography accessories
(5)
X-ray accessories
(10)
Records, transport and storage
(8)
X-ray/imaging markers
(14)
Cassette accessories and film
(5)
X-ray illuminators
(7)
Ct accessories
(3)
Diagnostic and evaluation tools
Welch allyn
(23)
Ri-scope
(4)
Diagnostic instruments and accessories
(13)
Dopplers
(4)
Fall management
Alarms and sensors
(36)
Alarm accessories
(8)
Injury prevention/risk identification
(33)
Patient room safety
(6)
Alimed one™ wireless fall monitoring system
(1)
Ergonomics
Office ergonomics
(66)
Healthcare ergonomics
(58)
Industrial ergonomics
(79)
Safety and ppe
(13)
Clinic & hospital supplies, equipment, furnishings
Gloves
(1)
Iv poles
(13)
Sundries
(2)
Glove box dispensers
(11)
Disinfectants
(2)
Disposables and single patient use
(5)
Wheelchair cushions
Economy gel wheelchair cushions
(13)
Premium gel wheelchair cushions
(10)
Premium foam wheelchair cushions
(5)
Replacement wheelchair cushion covers
(8)
Air cell wheelchair cushions
(16)
Positioning cushions
(28)
Specialty cushions
(9)
Economy foam wheelchair cushions
(13)
Operating room
Clinic furnishings
(230)
Surgical table accessories
(75)
Support surfaces
(70)
Anesthesia and respiratory
(61)
Clinical assessment
(30)
Surgical instruments
(119)
Operating room safety
(16)
Procedure tray kits
(2)
Stretchers, stretcher surfaces, and accessories
(4)
Other or supplies
(16)
Instrument care
(3)
Equipment covers
(15)
Sterilization and sterilization trays
(21)
Emergency preparedness
Er patient handling
(4)
Immobilization
(1)
Incident command
(2)
Emergency bedding/beds
(1)
Speech and language
Elderly/dementia
(8)
Dysphagia/oral motor
(22)
Adult speech and language
(14)
Cognition/brain injury
(12)
Communication
(5)
Speech and voice
(2)
Pediatrics
Pediatric orthotics
(41)
Pediatric pads and positioners
(3)
Pediatric mobility aids
(4)
Pediatric seating and positioning
(21)
Pediatric beds, bassinets and cribs
(10)
Pediatric speech therapy
(6)
Pediatric emergency medical carts
(2)
Pediatric diagnostics
(1)
Podiatry
Footwear
(95)
Heel protection
(34)
Forefoot solutions
(67)
Radiation protection
Radiation protection glasses
(17)
Radiation protection apron accessories
(4)
Radiation protection aprons
(18)
Radiation protection thyroid shields
(4)
Patient radiation protection
(4)
Radiation protection barriers & table shields
(8)
Radiation protection gloves
(7)
Radiation protection apron racks
(3)
Veterinary radiation protection
(1)
Infection control
Antimicrobials
(13)
Waste disposal and biohazard
(9)
Protection dispensers
(11)
Face mask dispensers
(1)
Isolation stations
(1)
Probe and transducer covers
(4)
Lab safety
(2)
Hand hygiene
(1)
Rehabilitation & physical therapy
Modalities
(87)
Wound care/skin protection
(102)
Exercise
(110)
Rehab positioners
(6)
Edema products
(19)
Test & evaluation
(10)
Restraints
(1)
Adl - aids for daily living
Dining aids
(56)
Toileting aids
(12)
Dressing aids
(17)
Reading, writing, computing aids
(3)
Bathing & hygiene aids
(17)
Reachers
(7)
Other self help aids
(2)
Self transfer aids
(5)
Medication aids
(2)
Household kitchen aids
(2)
Splints and braces
Foot and ankle braces and splints
(73)
Contracture braces
(71)
Spine supports and braces
(40)
Shoulder supports and braces
(28)
Plantar fasciitis solutions
(16)
Hand and wrist splints and braces
(42)
Orthotic and splinting materials
(93)
Knee braces and knee supports
(78)
Finger and thumb splints and braces
(51)
Elbow splints and braces
(28)
Hip and thigh splints and braces
(7)
Fracture splints and braces
(17)
Footwear, insoles, inserts
Insoles and inserts for shoes
(100)
Hosiery, socks and stockings
(13)
Never events
Pressure injuries
(16)
Elopement
(2)
Medical staff ppe
Disposable ppe
(1)
Face masks and face shields
(1)
Medical carts
Medical cart accessories
(33)
Isolation/infection control carts
(38)
Procedure/anesthesia medical carts
(71)
Emergency medical carts
(36)
Medical computer carts
(1)
Treatment carts
(10)
Specialty medical carts
(14)
Mri medical carts
(8)
Durable medical equipment
Commodes
(6)
Wheelchair essentials
(58)
Beds, mattresses and accessories
(17)
Bath safety
(13)
Bed positioning and safety
(38)
Walkers, canes and crutches
(29)
Geriatric chairs and accessories
(7)
Toilet risers and rails
(7)
Pillows
(4)
Wheelchairs
(31)
Hip chairs
(4)
Patient positioners
Aligel™ positioners
(20)
Alilite gel positioners
(9)
Foam positioners
(46)
Sandbags
(4)
Bean bag positioners
(3)
Freedom® gel positioners
(10)
Protecta-coat™ positioners
(7)
Lateral positioning
(2)
Invisicoat positioners
(2)
Medical Education Materials
Anatomical Charts
(26)
Anatomical Models
(15)
